ucan.org 2014-04-12

# UCAN - Utility Consumers' Action Network | San Diego - Privacy Policy

Your relationship with Utility Consumers’ Action Network is your business only.

We do not collect personally identifiable information on our web site or otherwise unless you choose to give it to us when registering, via email, a phone call, or by postal mail. Even when you choose to give us information, we keep it confidential.  
We do not sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose mailing lists or other personally identifiable information. We maintain some records of individuals who contact us in case we contact you later or provide further information to you in the future. However, we do not provide this information to anyone else unless you give us your permission.

On occasion we are asked by the media to provide the names of consumers who are willing to speak out on specific consumer issues. We do not share such names or other identifying information unless you specifically authorize us to do so.

UCAN agrees not to disclose a user’s personal information except in limited circumstances.  UCAN may disclose a user’s personal information when UCAN is subject to valid legal process or as required to provide to provide a user with the services the user requests.  UCAN will disclose information if it is required by law.  UCAN will post changes to their privacy policy 30 days in advance of the changes taking effect.  If a user terminates their account, UCAN will deactivate the specific user account, but UCAN retains the account in order to resolve disputes or enforce agreements.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
If you have registered to receive e-mail communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. You have the following options to do this:

You can send an e-mail to [contactus@ucan.org](mailto:contactus@ucan.org)

You can send mail to the following address:

Utility Consumers' Action Network  
3405 Kenyon Street, Suite 401  
San Diego, CA 92110

619-610-9010
